Guide to the Poly Archives Portrait Collection RG.028
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- F, 10317
  - Folan, Lorcan M., undated; cuid1292; 10358 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Ford, Frank J., 1957; cuid1293; 10359 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Foster, Ronald, 1954, 1955, 1956; cuid1294; 10376 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Fox, Beauvais, undated; cuid1295; 10377 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Fox, Jerome, undated; cuid1296; 10378 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Foxen, Richard William, 1997, 2000; cuid1297; 10379 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Fraim, P.B., undated; cuid1298; 10380 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Frankl, Phyllis, undated; cuid1299; 10381 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Freimark, Steve, undated; cuid1300; 10382 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Friedman, Leonard J., 2000; cuid1301; 10383 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Friedman, Rachelle, undated; cuid1302; 10384 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Frieman, Edward A., 1986, 1992; cuid1303; 10385 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Friend, William "Bill", 1985, 1993; cuid1304; 10386 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Frisch, Ivan, 1983, 1986, 1992, 1993; cuid1305; 10387 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Fritz, Brother Raymond L., 1977, 1996; cuid1306; 10388 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Frolich, Gerhard J., undated; cuid1307; 10389 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Fromm, Winfield E., 1974; cuid1308; 10390 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Frothingham, Isaac H., late 1880s; cuid1309; 10391 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Fruendlich, J., undated; cuid1310; 10392 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Fung, Haang, circa 1984; cuid1311; 10393 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Furnas, C.C., 1963; cuid1312; 10394 (Box 3, Folder 71)
- G, 10610
  - Gaines, W., undated; cuid1313; 10395 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Galil, Uzia, undated; cuid1314; 10396 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Galina, undated; cuid1315; 10397 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Gallagher, Evan, undated; cuid1316; 10398 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Gallagher, Jean, undated; cuid1317; 10399 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Galloway, E.C., undated; cuid1318; 10400 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Garbe, Edward, 1976; cuid1319; 10401 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Garcia, Jose, 2009; cuid1320; 10402 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Garetz, Bruce A., undated; cuid1321; 10403 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Garofalo, Frank, undated; cuid1322; 10404 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Garwin, Richard L., 2004; cuid1323; 10405 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Gavin, Joseph G., undated; cuid1324; 10406 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Gaylor, Walter, undated; cuid1325; 10407 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Gellis, Roberta, undated; cuid1326; 10408 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Gendel, Michael, undated; cuid1327; 10409 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Genovese, undated; cuid1328; 10410 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Georgakis, Christos, undated; cuid1329; 10411 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Georgi, Gunter, undated; cuid1330; 10412 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Gerhardt, Kenneth C., undated; cuid1331; 10413 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Gersten, Marvin C., 1980; cuid1332; 10414 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Gertler, Janos, undated; cuid1333; 10415 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Geva, Eran, 2009; cuid1334; 10416 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Ghandehari, Masoud, undated; cuid1335; 10417 (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Giacobello, Bartholemew F., 1981; cuid1336; 10418 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Giba, John, 1966, 1993, 1995; cuid1337; 10419 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Gilbert, Jack, undated; cuid1338; 10420 (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Gilbert, John, undated; cuid1339; 10421 (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Gillett, Elizabeth R.H., undated; cuid1340; 10422 (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Gillette, David, 2001; cuid1341; 10423 (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Gilmont, Roger, 1991; cuid1342; 10424 (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Giordano, Anthony B. (and wife Peggy), circa 1950, 1996; cuid1343; 10425 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Glenn, Alvin B., undated; cuid1344; 10426 (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Gluckman, Joshua, undated; cuid1345; 10427 (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Gobran, Riad, undated; cuid1346; 10428 (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Gold, Albert, 1978; cuid1347; 10429 (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Gold, Bernard, 1998; cuid1348; 10430 (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Gold, Lawrence, 1975; cuid1349; 10431 (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Gold, Louis, undated; cuid1350; 10432 (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Goldberg, Samuel David, 1968; cuid1351; 10433 (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Golden, William T., undated; cuid1352; 10434 (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Goldin, Daniel S., 1992; cuid1353; 10435 (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Goldman, David S., undated; cuid1354; 10436 (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Goldman, Irwin, 1977; cuid1355; 10437 (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - Goldman, Jack, undated; cuid1356; 10438 (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - Goldmark, Peter C., undated; cuid1357; 10439 (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - Goldsmith, Clifford Henry, 1996, 1998, 2001; cuid1358; 10440 (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - Goldstein, Harvey, 1993; cuid1359; 10441 (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - Goldstein, Matthew, undated; cuid1360; 10442 (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - Goodman, David J., 1999; cuid1361; 10443 (Box 3, Folder 120)
  - Goodman, Murray, undated; cuid1362; 10444 (Box 3, Folder 121)
  - Gordon, Emmet F., undated; cuid1363; 10445 (Box 3, Folder 122)
  - Gordon, Jayne, circa 1996; cuid1364; 10446 (Box 3, Folder 123)
  - Gould, Gordon, undated; cuid1365; 10447 (Box 3, Folder 124)
  - Grad, Arthur, 1971; cuid1366; 10448 (Box 3, Folder 125)
  - Granato, Richardson, undated; cuid1367; 10449 (Box 3, Folder 126)
  - Granis, Michael, 1957; cuid1368; 10450 (Box 3, Folder 127)
  - Grantz, Howard E., undated; cuid1369; 10451 (Box 3, Folder 128)
  - Grau, Herman, undated; cuid1370; 10452 (Box 3, Folder 129)
  - Gray, Lucille R., undated; cuid1371; 10453 (Box 3, Folder 130)
  - Gray, Nomer, undated; 9; 10454 (Box 3, Folder 131)
  - Grayson, Laurence, 1986; cuid1372; 10455 (Box 3, Folder 132)
  - Greco, William J., undated; cuid1373; 10456 (Box 3, Folder 133)
  - Green, Mark, 1994, 2002; cuid1374; 10457 (Box 3, Folder 134)
  - Greene, Barry, cuid1375; 13586 (Box 3, Folder 135)
  - Greenfield, S. Steve, 1988; cuid1376; 10458 (Box 3, Folder 136)
  - Greenshields, Bruce D., undated; cuid1377; 10459 (Box 3, Folder 137)
  - Greenwood, Doug, undated; cuid1378; 10460 (Box 3, Folder 138)
  - Gregor, Harry, 1955, 1958, 1962, 1964; cuid1379; 10461 (Box 3, Folder 139)
  - Grieco, Linda, undated; cuid1380; 10462 (Box 3, Folder 140)
  - Griemsmann, John, undated; cuid1381; 10463 (Box 3, Folder 141)
  - Griffis, Fletcher H. "Bud", 1999, 2000; cuid1382; 10464 (Box 3, Folder 142)
  - Grill, Jeanette, undated; cuid1383; 10465 (Box 3, Folder 143)
  - Gross, Richard A., 1998, 1999, 2000, 2001, 2004; cuid1384; 10466 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Gross, S.H., 1967; cuid1385; 10467 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Grossman, undated; cuid1386; 10468 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Grossman, Fred, 1978; cuid1387; 10469 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Gruber, Helmut, 1986; cuid1388; 10470 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Gruehr, Anatole R., 1956; cuid1389; 10471 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Guerrieri, Anne, undated; cuid1390; 10472 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Gugick, Leonard, undated; cuid1391; 10473 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Guglielmi, Marco, 1986; cuid1392; 10474 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Gupta, Sunil, circa 1996; cuid1393; 10536 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- H, 10611
  - Haas, Zygmunt, undated; cuid1394; 10537 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Habach, George F., undated; cuid1395; 10538 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Haddad, Richard, undated; cuid1396; 10539 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Hadimioglu, H., undated; cuid1397; 10540 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Hague, Bernard, 1929; cuid1398; 10541 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Hall, 1958; cuid1399; 10542 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Hallingby, Paul Jr., undated; cuid1400; 10543 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Halpern, Gregory, 1982; cuid1401; 10544 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Hammoud, Harry P., undated; cuid1402; 10545 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Hampden, Walter, undated; cuid1403; 10546 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Han, Chang Dae "Paul", 1974, 1986; cuid1404; 10547 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Hancock, Herbie, 2002; cuid1405; 10548 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Hanson, Jimmy, undated; cuid1406; 10549 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Hao, Xiaolong, undated; cuid1407; 10550 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Harazim, William, 1974; cuid1408; 10551 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Harker, David (1906-1991), undated; cuid1409; 10552 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Harris, Wanda, circa 1996; cuid1410; 10553 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Harrison, Gen, 1953; cuid1411; 10554 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Harrington, Paul R., undated; cuid1412; 10555 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Harrison, Shelley A., 1994; cuid1413; 10556 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Hartigan, Ellen F., circa 1990; cuid1414; 10557 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Hase, Leopold, undated; cuid1415; 10558 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Hastak, Makarand, undated; cuid1416; 10559 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Hauser, Norbert, undated; cuid1417; 10560 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Hausmann, Erich, undated; cuid1418; 10561 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Hayes, Christopher, undated; cuid1419; 10562 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Hebbert, C. Mark, circa 1955; cuid1420; 10563 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Hechhouse, Phil, undated; cuid1421; 10564 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Heckman, Leila, 1997; cuid1422; 10565 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Heinzelman, Fred, 1960, 1982; cuid1423; 10566 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Hellerstein, Lisa, undated; cuid1424; 10567 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Henderson, Annette, 1978; cuid1425; 10568 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Henkel, Herbert L., 1999; cuid1426; 10569 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Hennessey, Raymond G., 1974; cuid1427; 10570 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Henry, Otto, 1960; cuid1428; 10571 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Herbach, L., undated; cuid1429; 10572 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Herbst, Marc, undated; cuid1430; 10573 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Herr, Barber, undated; cuid1431; 10574 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Hertzberg, Constantine, 1990s; cuid1432; 10575 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Hessel, Alexander, undated; cuid1433; 10576 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Hewlett, William R., 1975; cuid1434; 10577 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Heyke, John E., Jr., undated; cuid1435; 10578 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Hibben, Samuel G., undated; cuid1436; 10579 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Hielscher, Andreas, undated; cuid1437; 10580 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Hiller, Maruin H., 1975; cuid1438; 10581 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Hinkaty, Charles J., 1997; cuid1439; 10582 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Hinte, Fred, 1980; cuid1440; 10583 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Hirayama, Kozo, 1978; cuid1441; 10584 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Hoadley, George B., undated; cuid1442; 10585 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Hochman, Jack, undated; cuid1443; 10586 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Hochstadt, Harry, 1964, 1988; cuid1444; 10587 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Hockney, Donald, 1979, 1982, 1986, circa 1996; cuid1445; 10588 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Hoff, Nicholas J., 1953, 1956; cuid1446; 10589 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Hoffman, Harmon F., undated; cuid1447; 10590 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Hoiberg, Svend, undated; cuid1448; 10591 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Holloway, Helen, 1959; cuid1449; 10592 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Holub, Helen and Helene, 1954; cuid1450; 10593 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Holzmacher, Robert G., undated; cuid1451; 10594 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Homberger, Conrad, undated; cuid1452; 10595 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Hommer, Henry F., undated; cuid1453; 10596 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Honser, George, undated; cuid1454; 10597 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Hooper, John W., 1954; cuid1455; 10598 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Hoover, Charles W., Jr., undated; cuid1456; 10599 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Hora, Michael, undated; cuid1457; 10600 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Horn, Paul, undated; cuid1458; 10601 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Horton, Edward Everett, 1967; cuid1459; 10602 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Horton, Lishia, undated; cuid1460; 10603 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Horvath, John S., 1980; cuid1461; 10604 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Horwitch, Mel, undated; cuid1462; 10605 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Hostetter, undated; cuid1463; 10606 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Hotzler, Russell K., undated; cuid1464; 10607 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Houlihan, undated; cuid1465; 10608 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Houser, George G., undated; cuid1466; 10609 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Houston, Theodore Warren, 1960; cuid1467; 10613 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Howard, C. Douglas, undated; cuid1468; 10619 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Howley, Eamon, undated; cuid1469; 10620 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Huber, Robert E., undated; cuid1470; 10614 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Hultin, Jerry MacArthur, undated; cuid1471; 10615 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Hummel, Susan Flynn, undated; cuid1472; 10621 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Hunt, Donald F., undated; cuid1473; 10616 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Huseland, Norman, undated; cuid1474; 10617 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Hutter, Rudolf, undated; cuid1475; 10618 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Hyman, Jocette, circa 1996; cuid1476; 10622 (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Hynn, Robert, undated; cuid1477; 10623 (Box 4, Folder 94)
- I, 10612
  - Iacono, John, undated; cuid1478; 10624 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Iacono, Margie, cuid1479; 10625 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Iafrate, G., undated; cuid1480; 10957 (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Iftekhar, Lamia, 2009; cuid1481; 10626 (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Immergut, Edmund H., 1979; cuid1482; 10627 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Ingham, Joanne, 1999; cuid1483; 10628 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Ingram, Maxwell, undated; cuid1484; 10629 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Iorio, Jeffrey, undated; cuid1485; 10630 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Ip, Tak-Cheung, undated; cuid1486; 10631 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Irani, Ray R., undated; cuid1487; 10632 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Iskander, Magued, undated; cuid1488; 10633 (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Ivanoff, Donald, 2002; cuid1489; 10634 (Box 4, Folder 106)
- J, 10635
  - Jacobs, Eddy, undated; cuid1490; 10636 (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Jacobs, Joseph J., 1936, 1975, 1978, 1981, 1982, 1985, 1986, 1990, 1994; cuid1491; 10637 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Jacobs, Linda, 1993; cuid1492; 10638 (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Jacobs, Zena, undated; cuid1493; 10639 (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Jahnke, Craig C., undated; cuid1494; 10640 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - James, Dorothy, undated; cuid1495; 10641 (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - Jansen, Albert F.W., undated; cuid1496; 10642 (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - Jansen, Colleen, undated; cuid1497; 10643 (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - Janssen, Gimter, 1939; cuid1498; 10644 (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - Jazwinski, Arthur, undated; cuid1499; 10645 (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - Jear, E., undated; cuid1500; 10646 (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - Jenkins, Carol, undated; cuid1501; 10647 (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - Jiang, Zhong-Ping, undated; cuid1502; 10648 (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - Johnson, Anthony, 1980s; cuid1503; 10649 (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - Johnson, D.H., undated; cuid1504; 10650 (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Johnson, I. Birger, 1980; cuid1505; 10651 (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - Jones, Barry, undated; cuid1506; 10652 (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - Jones, Francis T., undated; cuid1507; 10653 (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - Jonsson, Eric, undated; cuid1508; 10654 (Box 4, Folder 125)
  - Jordan, Peter, 1995; cuid1509; 10655 (Box 4, Folder 126)
  - Juran, Ilan, undated; cuid1510; 10656 (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - Jung, Check K., undated; cuid1511; 10657 (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - Juretschke, Hellmut J., undated; cuid1512; 10658 (Box 4, Folder 129)
- K, 10659
  - Kabasakalian, Peter, undated; cuid1513; 10660 (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - Kaczmarek, Richard F., 1973; cuid1514; 10661 (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - Kadik, Abdelhamid, undated; cuid1515; 10662 (Box 4, Folder 132)
  - Kahn, Alexander, undated; cuid1516; 10663 (Box 4, Folder 133)
  - Kahn, Herman (1922-1983), undated; cuid1517; 10664 (Box 4, Folder 134)
  - Kahn, Sophie, undated; cuid1518; 10665 (Box 4, Folder 135)
  - Kahne, Stephen, undated; cuid1519; 10666 (Box 4, Folder 136)
  - Kalil, James, undated; cuid1520; 10667 (Box 4, Folder 137)
  - Kalkhoran, Iraj M., undated; cuid1521; 10668 (Box 4, Folder 138)
  - Kalotay, Andrew, undated; cuid1522; 10669 (Box 4, Folder 139)
  - Kammen, Michael, undated; cuid1523; 10670 (Box 4, Folder 140)
  - Kane, Jasper, 1995; cuid1524; 10671 (Box 4, Folder 141)
  - Kangas, Edward A., 2000; cuid1525; 10672 (Box 4, Folder 142)
  - Kapfer, (William H.), undated; cuid1526; 10673 (Box 4, Folder 143)
  - Kapila, Vikram, undated; cuid1527; 10674 (Box 4, Folder 144)
  - Kaplan, David, undated; cuid1528; 10675 (Box 4, Folder 145)
  - Kaplan, Helene, undated; cuid1529; 10676 (Box 4, Folder 146)
  - Kaplan, Joseph, 1957; cuid1530; 10677 (Box 4, Folder 147)
  - Kaplan, Seymour, 1986; cuid1531; 10678 (Box 4, Folder 148)
  - Kappaz, Michael H., 2010; cuid1532; 10679 (Box 4, Folder 149)
  - Kappenburg, William, undated; cuid1533; 10680 (Box 4, Folder 150)
  - Karnaugh, Maurice, undated; cuid1534; 10681 (Box 4, Folder 151)
  - Karri, Ramesh, undated; cuid1535; 10682 (Box 4, Folder 152)
  - Kasper, Victor Jr., undated; cuid1536; 10683 (Box 4, Folder 153)
  - Kastarelos, Konstantinos, undated; cuid1537; 10684 (Box 4, Folder 154)
  - Katchalski (Katzir), Ephraim, 1973, 1979; cuid1538; 10685 (Box 4, Folder 155)
  - Katsaggelos, Aggelos K., 1986; cuid1539; 10686 (Box 4, Folder 156)
  - Katz, J. Lawrence, undated; cuid1540; 10687 (Box 4, Folder 157)
  - Katz, Larry W., undated; cuid1541; 10688 (Box 4, Folder 158)
  - Katzen, Raphael, 1977; cuid1542; 10689 (Box 4, Folder 159)
  - Kaufman, Harold, 1986; cuid1543; 10690 (Box 4, Folder 160)
  - Kaufman, Michael D., 1996; cuid1544; 10691 (Box 4, Folder 161)
  - Kavanagh, Thomas C., undated; cuid1545; 10692 (Box 4, Folder 162)
  - Keenan, A.J., 1974; cuid1546; 10693 (Box 4, Folder 163)
  - Kellogg, Brainerd, undated; cuid1547; 10694 (Box 4, Folder 164)
  - Kelly, John, undated; cuid1548; 10695 (Box 4, Folder 165)
  - Kemp, L. Franklin, undated; cuid1549; 10696 (Box 4, Folder 166)
  - Kemper, Joseph, undated; cuid1550; 10697 (Box 4, Folder 167)
  - Kerge, Steve, undated; cuid1551; 10698 (Box 4, Folder 168)
  - Kerr, Michelle, undated; cuid1552; 10699 (Box 4, Folder 169)
  - Kershenbaum, Aaron, undated; cuid1553; 10700 (Box 4, Folder 170)
  - Kertesz, Dennis J., undated; cuid1554; 10701 (Box 4, Folder 171)
  - Keyworth, George A., undated; cuid1555; 10702 (Box 4, Folder 172)
  - Khaimchayev, Tamara, undated; cuid1556; 10703 (Box 4, Folder 173)
  - Khan, Eakalak, undated; cuid1557; 10704 (Box 4, Folder 174)
  - Khorrami, Farshad, 1995; cuid1558; 10705 (Box 4, Folder 175)
  - King, Carolyn D., undated; cuid1559; 10706 (Box 4, Folder 176)
  - Kinsey, Henry R., undated; cuid1560; 10707 (Box 4, Folder 177)
  - Kirk, Raymond E., 1955; cuid1561; 10708 (Box 4, Folder 178)
  - Kjeldaas, Terje, undated; cuid1562; 10709 (Box 4, Folder 179)
  - Kleiner, Eugene, 1986; cuid1563; 10710 (Box 4, Folder 180)
  - Kline, Tom, undated; cuid1564; 10958 (Box 4, Folder 181)
  - Klosner, Jerome, 1978; cuid1565; 10711 (Box 4, Folder 182)
  - Knudson, John Immanuel, 1935, 1953, 1954; cuid1566; 10712 (Box 4, Folder 183)
  - Kobayakawa, Shinya, 1998; cuid1567; 10713 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Kobayashi, Koji, undated; cuid1568; 10714 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Koch, Ed, udnated; cuid1569; 10715 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Koehler, George R., undated; cuid1570; 10716 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Koeing, undated; cuid1571; 10717 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Korfage, Willard, undated; cuid1572; 10718 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Korman, Samuel, 1956; cuid1573; 10719 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Korniczky, Stephen S., undated; cuid1574; 10720 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Kossay, David, 1959; cuid1575; 10721 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Kouar, Mohammed, undated; cuid1576; 10722 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Kozol, Lauren, undated; cuid1577; 10723 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Kramer (Kramer-Koehler), Pamela E., 1978, 1986; cuid1578; 10724 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Kramer, William, 2002; cuid1579; 10725 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Kreiling, Fred, 1979; cuid1580; 10726 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Kremer, Richard H., undated; cuid1581; 10727 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Kriftcher, Noel N., 2002; cuid1582; 10728 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Kristol, Irving, undated; cuid1583; 10729 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Kubat, Joseph E., undated; cuid1584; 10730 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Kuiken, Kathryn, undated; cuid1585; 10731 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Kumar, Sunil, undated; cuid1586; 10732 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Kunhardt, Erich, 1986; cuid1587; 10733 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Kuo, Spencer P., 1995, 1999; cuid1588; 10734 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Kurz, Ludwik, 1986; cuid1589; 10735 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Kwartler, A., circa 1968; cuid1590; 10736 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Kwei, T.K., undated; cuid1591; 10737 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- L, 10738
  - Lago, James, cuid1592; 10739 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Lai, Jai-Lu L. (J.L.), undated; cuid1593; 10740 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - LaMarsh, John, 1974; cuid1594; 10741 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Lan, Chuan-Tan Edward, undated; cuid1595; 10742 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Landis, undated; cuid1596; 10743 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Lando, Jerome, undated; cuid1597; 10744 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Landau, Gad. M., undated; cuid1598; 10745 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Lane, "Coach", 1955; cuid1599; 10746 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Lane, V. Hugo, undated; cuid1600; 10747 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Lannon, John, undated; cuid1601; 10748 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Larkin, Michael, 1997; cuid1602; 10749 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Lassen, Walter C., 1979; cuid1603; 10750 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Laster, Richard, 1974; cuid1604; 10751 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - LaTourette, James, undated; cuid1605; 10752 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Lauren, Sidney, undated; cuid1606; 10753 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Lawson, Richard, circa 1937; cuid1607; 10754 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Lederman, Peter, 1964; cuid1608; 10755 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Lee, Bernard S., undated; cuid1609; 10756 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Lee, C., undated; cuid1610; 10757 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Lee, David M., undated; cuid1611; 10758 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Lee, Marvin, undated; cuid1612; 10759 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Leeb, Leonard, 1978; cuid1613; 10760 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Lehman, Sheila, undated; cuid1614; 10761 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Leiber, Frank, undated; cuid1615; 10762 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Leistner, William E, 1985; cuid1616; 10763 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - LeKashman, John Q., 1974; cuid1617; 10764 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Lemelson, Jerome H., 1995, 1999; cuid1618; 10765 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Lender, Samuel, undated; cuid1619; 10766 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Lengyel, Emil, 1938; cuid1620; 10767 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Lentz, Robert H., undated; cuid1621; 10768 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Leonard, Martha R., 1987; cuid1622; 10769 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - LePaw, Sylvia, undated; cuid1623; 10770 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Lenz, Edward, 1937; cuid1624; 10771 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Leung, Kok-Ming, 1998; cuid1625; 10772 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Levi, Enrico, 1998; cuid1626; 10773 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Levine, Nathan, undated; cuid1627; 10774 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Levitt, Ian, undated; cuid1628; 10775 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Levon, Kalle, 1997, 2000; cuid1629; 10776 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Levy, Joel H., undated; cuid1630; 10777 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Levy, Leon, 1992, 1998; cuid1631; 10778 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Levy, Stephen, undated; cuid1632; 10779 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Lewin, Menachem, undated; cuid1633; 10780 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Lewis, James P., undated; cuid1634; 10781 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Lewis, Robert E., 1960, 1966; cuid1635; 10782 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Li, Joan, circa 1996; cuid1636; 10783 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Lian, Kenneth, undated; cuid1637; 10784 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Libby, Paul, undated; cuid1638; 10785 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Liccardi, Anthony, undated; cuid1639; 10786 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Lieber, Art, undated; cuid1640; 10787 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Lieberman, Burton, undated; cuid1641; 10788 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Likel, Harry C., undated; cuid1642; 10789 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Likourezos, George, undated; cuid1643; 10790 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Lin, Feng-Bao, undated; cuid1644; 10791 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Lin, Li-Chieh, undated; cuid1645; 10792 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Lindenauer, Abraham, undated; cuid1646; 10793 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Lindholm, undated; cuid1647; 10794 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Lindsay, John, undated; cuid1648; 10795 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Link, O. Winston, 1995; cuid1649; 10796 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Link, O. Winston -- Photos by, undated; cuid1650; 10797 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Linton, Jonathan D., undated; cuid1651; 10798 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Linza, Stuart, undated; cuid1652; 10799 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Lipitz, Elliott A., undated; cuid1653; 10800 (Box 5, Folder 87)